This for everyone for
fundraising okay There's this
concept that I learned
and we developed at
Fandroid early on called
walking up the then
down the What this
means is that most
founders they're go for
the biggest names VCs
first They go for
like the hottest names
they go for like
people who have like
good signal right But
those people are at
the top of the
ladder We encourage founders
to walk up the
first So you go
for other folks who
are like you and
maybe there's like a
new VC in and
then they just raised
like a small pocket
of but they're you
they're to Like get
some of these newer
names first Maybe there
certain angels whatever Like
in multiple rounds you
can still get angels
involved Angels like I
customers or something So
you kind of stack
up And some of
these like they could
even be like we've
gotten a of Taiwanese
capital into Southeast Asian
startups recently Like we've
always had a great
relationship with Taiwan and
VCs And so maybe
you get some of
the who are like
say not the usual
suspects Now if you
start stacking up let's
say you're raising 2
million right And you
got like one and
million dollars from all
kinds of then you
go to the name
that you want And
you say hey Studio
65 VC I have
half my round of
my 3 closed You
want to get in
or not Yeah you
and we're closing out
the rest of the
tough pretty soon but
somebody recommended I speak
to you right My
friend who is your
profile company environment I
speak to you but
we don't have too
much time But just
you know wanted to
just take up on
this thing right